Let me tell you a little cheat code.
If you're a personal trainer
and you want to do well as a personal
trainer, don't
be a classic personal trainer bellend,
which I'm afraid you
are doing here. Your job
is not to be jacked.
Your job is not to show off your muscles.
Your job is not to show us your workouts.
Your fucking job is to help people with
the problems that they face on a
daily basis.
And if you can help them with those
problems online, they will
hire you.
But if you make this all about you,
you're just looking at other fitness
bellends and taking advice from them.
They're all broke. They all have no money.
They all live at home with their parents.
And you will get in the same fucking trap
if you do not
realize that everything you do
is about solving people's problems
online. And it just doesn't look to me,
what I eat in a day.
Start solving problems. Don't know
if you've got any clients.
If you do have any clients,
write a fucking list of the 10 biggest
problems they
face, go solve them, because guess what?
Sandra in the gym feels sorry for you,
and you're helping her get rid of her
bingo
wings and drop 15 pounds before she goes
to Benidorm next door.
There's fucking a few Sandras out there
that could hire you